is harder than that bro i'm like what
the [__] do i tell them like how do i
say this no
no okay all right you want to make 300
bucks like easy no thanks
you want to make like 300 bucks in like
20 minutes for a youtube channel no
sorry
what's your name
josh my name is alex you want to make
300 bucks
we've been trying to do this for like 30
40 minutes and nobody's down to [__]
make 300 bucks and what is it 30 minutes
all right so i trade forks
i teach people how to trade
oh for forks yeah oh fire perfect yeah
so like like you know i can teach people
how to drink so i'm gonna teach you like
how long have you been doing it
i've been doing it for
a month bro and i only watch some
youtube videos
all right so we just found what was your
name josh josh appreciate you guys for
following up so we were leaving the
starbucks um drive-thru i'm like yo that
guy that guy in the world let's let's
get him in the car he looks young so i'm
like probably somebody young knows how
to trade he says he's training for how
long a month a month yeah i just like i
just don't watch your youtube videos
you've been watching youtube yeah okay
so like we like the ideal thing we were
gonna do now is i was gonna connect to
the like starbucks wi-fi or some type of
wi-fi and i was gonna teach him here but
bro there's like no wi-fi none of our
hot spots are working so i'm gonna tell
him you leave you set a three right
three
three yeah so when he leaves work at
three he's gonna pull up to the office
the the vote uh the level up vote and
then basically he has no idea what it is
yeah like he has no idea so he pulls up
he's gonna see he has like no idea so
when he pulls up then i'm gonna teach
him um the three basic things that i
think is going to help him like shorten
his learning curve because you're
telling me your your boy this training
tool yeah yeah he's been training for uh
less than a year six months but he's
been
like researching it for like a year yeah
so he's been training trading for six
months yeah but trust me like what i'm
gonna teach you like later today when
you come like it's gonna shorten your
learning curve by like six to eight
months yeah but i'm gonna give you guys
two videos be too long yeah now they're
long like there's just too much
information out there oh i i i feel
overwhelmed for sure overall for real
like i sometimes i don't know to take
notes not to take notes to like just
watch the video then watch it again i
don't know what to do i got you when you
pull over i mean you stay like you're in
the right way i stay down south but you
could pull up no big deal all right
perfect all right all right so you guys
will see him at the boat
alex has a serious cake pop addition not
even just a cake pop addiction a pink
cake pop addiction let me get one cake
pop ah one cake pop okay
which one do you want the
birthday kpop chocolate
chip cookies
birthday
needs help
so he just pulled up he just got out of
work right now we just you know getting
him here at the hq we got raul on the
other side
you got him yeah yeah you probably hear
that so we're gonna go inside now and
i'm gonna show you the three basic
principles of trading so he mainly
trades like options um you say trade on
weibo right yeah on weeble so we're
gonna show him like you know what uh
tradingview is metatrader and kind of to
get him like the feel of the most for me
the most important things when it comes
to trading which is the trend supply and
demand support and resistance and then
entry signals let's go into the hq bro
so this is like our level up hq as you
guys can see it's a work in progress so
this has kind of been here for like
like a month already we've had this just
like chilling
okay whatever so we have our map if you
guys haven't seen our map let me give
you like this place has a name already
yeah oh yeah it's called the vote right
so we did a poll on our discord if you
guys went and voted basically we had
three different names was it diamond
club diamond district they were
different yeah there was like 10.
yeah and then the vote is the one that
won right so we got this map that we're
gonna basically hang up uh on that wall
right there because every single trader
when they come in to trade through a
podcast or whatever they're going to
mark up the country they're coming from
you know we have traders all around the
world but the other day we had a payout
from nabia i bet you don't even know
where nabi is i don't know what it is
it's in africa like we have people
trading in africa bro let's do it so
that's like insane right so um we have
the certificate wall we're not done with
it we have a bunch of them that we still
have to put up
um we have casing for an event that we
have coming very soon and then let's go
upstairs so we show him how to trade all
right so this is like a work in progress
right now this is um kind of like a
recording station um for bianca you guys
haven't seen the bianca's videos make
sure to check out the instagram we have
like a little podcast studio for all of
our profitable traders where we're gonna
come and interview them hopefully this
guy levels up and we get him on the
podcast now so that'd be dope
so let's get this guy to get the basics
right pretty simple
all right look so now that we're here in
the charts this is very simple right so
let me actually just give you a very
simple basic foundation in trading right
so we all know the markets obviously
move up they move in an uptrend
and then they move in a downtrend right
you know this is pretty standard yeah
when it comes to options you don't you i
know cells are put so you do play yeah
you can put yeah okay and then you
obviously take buys right yeah all right
so in all markets but mainly in forex
it's a lot you know
very uh common that there's uptrends
then there's a [__] ton of
consolidations and then there's
downtrends right so
first thing first that you want to
get to know when it comes to trading and
be like make this your best friend get
this tattoo do whatever
trend is your friend like if the
market's going up trust me bro like you
want to be going up with the market like
if the market is somewhere within this
push to the upside you want to be
looking for buys in here if the market
is on the downtrend you want to be
looking for sales if the market is in
this range bro do not even like bother
to get involved that's why there's a
bunch of other different markets to
trade right that's why we don't stick to
one pair like the approach to the market
the purchase of the market is the same
on like on any pair right so first
things first the trend is your friend
how do you identify a trend by higher
highs and higher lows do you know what
those are yeah you know what highers are
okay so all right let's see let's see if
it's true all right so what is this
point right here higher high all right
what is
this point right here
higher low okay what's this point
all right what about
this one
higher low no it's not a higher light it
only would be a higher low if it's
okay it makes a higher high right
because this right here could have had
this yeah push here then done something
like this and then gone yeah so it's not
it's not okay so it's technically not a
higher low and so it doesn't get a
higher height this is like a huge gem
for all of you guys out there the only
way you get a higher high is if there's
a higher low there's there's no higher
low unless it's a higher high right
that's a huge jump all right let's see
for the downtrend what would
this point be
a higher low no
lower a lower something a lower low
lower low all right so if this is a
lower low what's this one
lower high perfect all right all right
back all right all right what's this
point right here what is this point
lower low all right what's this point
lower high all right what's this what's
this point
well it's not it's not
all right because it's the same [__]
right because like like there's like a
little trick that nobody for some reason
knows you just flip the scale and it's
the same thing as downside to the upside
you see how you can just flip it you
know pretty easy so the first things
first is you need to identify whether
the market is bullish or bearish and the
first way you identify that is by higher
highs and higher lows so we're gonna put
this here number one trust me
bro this is gonna make or break people's
trading because a lot of people they
don't like they just wanna feel involved
in the markets and if the market isn't
giving you a trend bro there's no reason
to be involved in the market right okay
so what would you
where did this thing go let's see if we
can find it
right here all right so what would you
call this market as of right now like
what is this market is this a bullish
market or a bearish market
well you said if it was going up
if it was creating higher highs
it would be uh bullish okay and then if
it was creating both of those it would
be bearish okay yeah i'm fine yeah so
so that's
well it's it's bullish
this is bugs you sure yeah you're 100
sure i'm not 100 percent oh nice so you
[__] up you got to be 100 right yeah
you're right i'm just testing you all
right look so this is bullish why like
where would you mark up the higher high
point let's see if you get this bro you
got you get the hundred bucks like yeah
you already got 100 bucks easy fast uh
what would i mark up my higher high yeah
it would be all right so all right let's
list this i'm gonna give you three
points is it gonna be point one should
is it gonna be point
one
is it gonna be point two
or is it gonna be point
nine three it's gonna be point two
my [__] man bro all right that's a
100 bucks all right [__] it all right
yo you gotta get 100 bucks
all right fire because you got it
all right so
very easy first thing he sees when he
comes into the markets without even
looking at the market you without like
without looking at the market structure
you could already see that it's bullets
you're seeing how it's heading to the
upside right and then when you look at
it into a little bit more detail you can
see clear market structure that is
creating higher higher yeah all right
let's list i'm going to give you a bonus
dollars if you can mark up the higher
low right so if this is the higher high
where would the higher low be
so i'm going to give you three options i
mean this is easy 100 bucks bro
one
two
four
three which one would the higher low be
uh
[Music]
three
[__] up bro oh cause because of the
because it hasn't reached it
exactly exactly all right don't worry
you got you got other opportunities now
right so this would be the higher low
because this is what created the higher
high yeah correct you've seen it so i
need because it needs a higher high to
create exactly exactly so that's the
first thing we set on the last one and
yeah if this one is above this point
then this is a higher high and this
turns into the higher level okay fire no
problem this is the you know you gotta
you got to learn you're living right so
this is where we keep it going right so
the first things first the trend is your
friend right so we got that out the way
you ran up 100.
so now two the second thing would be
support and resistance right supporting
resistance that we were talking about
liquidity it's all the stuff right so
let's go back to a basic line chart
right so obviously the market moves how
we already established in an uptrend
and then the market moves in a downtrend
right very simple very clean super easy
right but within these structure moves
there's levels of
resistance
as you can see it's a level of
resistance a level of support a level of
support now used as resistance right as
well as here you can see this is a level
of resistance support resistance right
you're seeing how the same level that is
used as resistance can be used as
support
in this case whenever you are above so
let's go down here right so whenever
you're on an uptrend
you want to be buying at a level that
has been used as resistance
to now be potentially used as support to
have the move to the upside okay right
so every single time we have a higher
high we want our higher low
at our previous structure point or
anywhere where it's supporting
resistance so then we have the next push
to the upside right because it can pass
our previous structure but then it
literally stops yeah yeah so yeah
exactly so if we were to break this
point it comes into the next level of
support you're trying to buy out of
support so whether it's this one or this
one you need to buy the support yeah
that it gets me confused the part where
like uh
what which one is resistance on the
downtrend and which one support and then
on the uptrend which one support so like
one line for example like here like this
zone right here is resistance when
you're under it and when you're above it
it's support okay so let's say this case
right here we're above it but let's say
this for some reason breaks under we
could come back use it as resistance and
then we sell oh
you get what i mean like basically this
is this is a zone
if you're above it you're buying if
you're under it yourself okay it's
really that simple so if you're on an
uptrend and you're above the zone you
want to buy at that zone let's say price
is right here you can't buy just yet
because you're not at the zone you get
what i mean like you need price to get
to the zone in order to buy
right so same thing when a market is
going in a downtrend let's say the
market is heading to the downside we're
having lows and highs
this level of support is now used as
resistance
right so this level of resistance then
we'll create a
lower low so we wanted to come back and
then retest this support as resistance
you're kind of seeing it yeah all right
what do you see more clean do you see
more clean the buys or the seats no for
sure the buys for sure the buys look
more clean right yeah so this is like a
little trick going off like sidetrack
this for all of you guys out there as
well like whenever the market is let's
say in a selling market and then you
can't see it clear so let's say for
example this zone right here let's just
mark it off let's say you're in this
zone and the cells are clean right
because i know how to look at the market
already but you're having difficulties
you can just pull up and then you flip
it and then you see how now it looks a
lot cleaner because it's um
how to do it so it's just right click so
yeah you right click on this on the and
then you click invert scale all right
and that's it right so so that's like a
little trick but the main thing is that
it's support and resistance right like
you're buying at a support support is a
floor and then you're selling at a
resistance right yeah simple yeah all
right but let's see so when we pull up
here to the charts
mark up a level of resistance that was
used as support
so like get this box right here and then
just like do a horizontal line wherever
a resistance is used as support
okay easy another hundred bucks you get
a second but whatever
all right no wait now you so you just
got support used as resistance so now
find me a resistance you know find me a
support and i use this resistance so you
did it obviously now on an uptrend so
you're obviously better at identifying
uptrends so now do it for me vice versa
find me one that is
on the downtrend right so let's go find
we find the downtrend yeah
like this one okay and then
um
what if we try to invert it
and then see if i can get it
no that [__] just got trippy right
it did
because now it's bullish
if there's nothing clean you can keep
going back and you can find something
else like like look more to the left
okay
um
right
when i click this yeah do you want me to
invert it back yeah i'm ready back
fire
damn
damn you lost it oh that's my elastic
right yeah it's trippy that's why like
it's just like a little trick that helps
oh it's right here
there it is it's right here
it's a level of support used as
resistance perfect all right easy
another hundred bucks all right it's
easy right yeah yeah all right and now
we have the third thing and for me the
third thing would be you need to have an
entry signal so this is going to be
super tricky there's a lot of different
types of entry signals if you guys
haven't read candlestick bible i highly
recommend you guys going it's a book
yeah it's a book that tells you
literally all of the candlesticks for
you to like like for enter yeah entry so
handle stick and then the only
candlestick pattern or entry or whatever
i know is um it's the one where like you
use the fibonacci replacement
make sure it's above the
but you got but you got like a hammer
okay yeah perfect exactly yeah yeah bro
so you you know your [__] bro this is
pretty crazy so i mean like i personally
like using engulfings and engulfing yeah
that's the thing i can never find them
because okay so you'll have a
candlestick that's like this right and
then the youtuber will be like or
whoever i'm watching right will be like
okay there's a candlestick that's like
this right and they'll call it an
engulfing but they say that like
engulfing has to be around
yeah i mean it's like this look but
there's literally engulfing everywhere
like like there's an engulfing basically
right here there's an engulfing right
here yeah so if you notice
this is the engulfing pattern right here
okay this is the engulfing pattern right
but it could be one multiple
candlesticks as well yeah actually
you're looking for one ideally like i i
want something like this like ideally
for me i want something like this i want
this one candlestick this bullish
engulfing to engulf like one or two
previous candles oh so so it shows like
rejection right so when you have an
uptrend right so that when you have an
uptrend you have a trend to the upside
and you have price that's come back to
retest your level of resistance as
support right you're with me so far yeah
at this area right here this is where
i'll look for my entry signal so this is
where i'll get let's say a doji so i'll
get a candlestick that kind of looks
like this one
right it looks like a little cross
you've seen this before right yeah yeah
i've definitely seen one so once you get
the cross i need an engulfing to engulf
that candlestick from this area of
interest
you get me yes so
let's see find me an engulfing
with a similar thing like this literally
break retest resistance you just support
uptrend and go okay wow
it's your last opportunity to the
easiest hundred bucks you've ever made
let's do it on this time so you got like
you're on a time span it's like 35
seconds all right not kidding
you go as far back left as you want
hold up i want to make this challenging
though so do you see one here like if
you see one
do i see one yeah
no i don't see him
i mean there's one yeah no i see one for
sure
okay okay fair enough because then it's
on an uptrend okay
but it would have to continue on enough
yeah yeah so i mean this is good i see
what you did basically this is the level
of
resistance here break retest the
engulfing the more ideal one would have
been like this one right here as you can
see we are
bullish on the upside yeah and then this
is the retest resistance to the support
look at the oh okay
and these aren't trays that played out
fully ideally yeah like you know we want
this tray to have like a fully full like
that but like you know it's just more of
like the principal so that's so easy so
where are we at like
50 bucks
not right where are we at
i don't know no no that's fire all right
simple so i mean what do you think like
what do you think of like this is simple
yeah and so do you see how i just did
that yeah so you see how it just did
that right there the red one yeah that's
the part where i would get messed up on
you feel me like i would place a trade
somewhere where i thought it would keep
it continue going up and then it would
just consolidate like where i put it and
then it would go back down yeah well i
mean then that's where we would have to
get on to like another video yeah and
then i'd have to show you like top down
analysis and like understand where you
are in the moon okay like are you at the
top of the move are you are you going to
exactly so like that's where like a lot
of people mess up because like if you
notice where you drew the line like yeah
that you were buying on the four hour
yeah but on the daily you're pulling up
to like a daily support used as
resistance you got me so there's so much
more that goes into it than just those
three those are just like the
foundations that you need you feel me so
i mean i got you i could hook you up
with plenty more i mean if you guys want
to see him on another video you guys let
me know we have a meet and greet that
we're going to do here soon you guys
will probably see like the aftermath of
this because it's going to be uploaded
after that but yeah he's going to pull
up he's going to get to meet all of the
other traders and like the community and
stuff so i mean appreciate you bro easy
easy 200 bucks you made man appreciate
you coming hit the thumbs up
all right all right let's do this let's
do this if this video is like there's
like some milk boy stuff it's like with
the nuggets yeah if this video gets
i don't know what do i usually get
yeah what do i usually get if this video
i i'll see now like the numbers if this
video gets a certain amount of likes and
a certain amount of comments i'll bring
him back and then your buddy yeah all
right you said you're gonna be so dope
okay that'd be so dope okay fire we
bring you and you're like he's like shy
so i could do the talking okay
all right so if this video gets anywhere
from 2 000 to 3 000 likes and let's say
500 comments we'll get him back on a
part two so the moment that happens you
guys already know yeah you can continue
the the part that you're gonna tell me
yeah you're gonna you're gonna keep
making more money bro
he only ended up getting two so like i
said make sure that like comment
subscribe this video gets two to twenty
five hundred likes we're him back so
here's uh 200 bucks for you bro
appreciate you man i appreciate you
having me on glad to have you here so we
put on the podcast with a b because it's
kind of like a b
um i like reminds me kind of him because
you know he becomes like from like a
like hard working background this guy's
working hard right now so like i told
him to watch the podcast get to the
channel so he kind of gets more
motivated so like comment subscribe so
you guys take him on a part two